One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Beyond the heavy rain is a rainbow
hageshii ame no mukou kakaru niji wo mita
I'll know the easy answer's a lie
tayasui kotae wa uso dato shiru darou
Vow not to back down to the shouting
dekai koe nanka ni makenai to chikatte
I need you alone to understand tomorrow
anata hitori ni wakatte hoshii ashita
You gave me the time of my life
yume no youna jikan kureta anata
What do I look like? An ANGEL or a DEVIL...
watashi wa dou mieteruno? sorega tenshi ka akuma ka
Beyond the dawn, beyond the dawn
yoake no mukou yoake no mukou
There's so much I want to tell you
hanashitai koto takusan arun da
Filled with love, with love
ai kometa ai kometa
That can't be written down in a letter
tegami ni kakikirenai omoi da
A small hand in search of eternity
eien wo sagashita chiisana tenohira
Nika?
That's right, he's my idol.
He appears from the blue
with laughter and this rythm.
"Kuma's Life"
2 YEARS AGO
Hey, Bonney!
Bonney!
Jeez!
Don't call me Bonney!
C-ap-ta-in!
Alright, alright, Captain!
This island right here!
Kumachi must be there!
What? Are you sure?!
I'm pretty sure!
But the thing is, the Marines are also here...
Dad!
Let's go, guys!
Disembark!
It's the Bonney Pirates!
There's a fleet-wide order for their arrest!
They say injured elders and children
are left lying in their wake!
What?!
Targeting only the weak!
They're absolute trash!
Shoot!
Get out of my way!
Age Skewer!
Kumachi! Where are you?! Show yourself!
A giant man?
Yes, I just saw him at the edge of town!
- Captain Bonney!
- Someone saw Kumachi!
Be right there!
- Where?!
- He said he was that way!
Okay!
We must not meet.
Bonney, please understand.
Don't look for me.
Why wasn't he there?!
Look, we're all pirates now, so let's
take our time searching, Captain.
Nika, huh?
Then I wanna look for Nika, too!
When I see Dad,
he'll be happy if I tell him
I found Nika on an island somewhere.
Meanwhile in the East Blue
Meanwhile in the East Blue...
Gum-Gum...
...Battle Axe!
After defeating Arlong's crew,
part of the Fish-Man Pirates,
Straw Hat Luffy rose to
prominence as a pirate.
Yay! I got a bounty on my head!
"Straw Hat Luffy"
Luffy"
I'm going to Loguetown.
Loguetown? For what?
Well... By the way,
who oversees that area?
Captain Smoker does.
oker does.
"Defeated the Arlong Pirates"
Jinbe, Jinbe!
Guess whose little brother he is!
The answer is my little brother!
What?! The kid who beat
the Arlong Pirates is your brother?!
It's funny, Dragon...
Both of our children became pirates...
These are the ironclad laws
of piratey behavior!
Plunder whatever you want!
Plunder!
Only from bad guys!
Don't help people!
Don't!
Unless they need it!
Like this?
That's it!
I think that's how you wear lipstick.
Yes! I'm all grown-up!
If I don't put something on my cheek,
Dad might not recognize me.
And...
...I should become famous!
Then I'm sure he'll notice me!
Right, Dad?
Egghead,
New World
I find this creepy.
I'm not surprised.
Clone soldier production is going
well, just like your modifications.
Anyway, have you heard about the boy who
declared war against the World Government?
Shoot down that flag.
Roger.
What?! He's Dragon's son?!
You'll see my memories anyway,
so there's no point in hiding it from you.
Coincidence or not, he also defies the Government with his rubber powers.
He is exactly like Nika, my hero.
You're right.
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Jet Shell!
Thriller Bark,
Grand Line
My mission is to exterminate every single one of you, but...
I want you to bring me Straw Hat Luffy's head.
As long as they have him, the Government won't mind.
Betray our comrade...?!
We refuse!
Such a shame.
Ursa Shock!
Then, go ahead and take it...
But not his head!
I beg you to take my life instead of his!
Luffy's the man who is gonna
be the Pirate King!
If you really intend to take his place,
then you must literally share his suffering.
This would even knock me unconscious.
He has good friends.
As expected from your son,
Dragon.
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Seven Warlords, mandatory summons!
Refuse, and your title will be revoked!
Don't be so dramatic. What's this about?
The bannerman of the new generation,
Portgas D. Ace's public execution is now set.
That means there will be war
with the Whitebeard Pirates!
War with Whitebeard?
I'll definitely be there in time.
Sabaody Archipelago
Isn't the food here yet?!
We're running out of it!
Get me more pizza!
It seems they're cooking it as
fast as they can, Captain.
They won't make it in time, at this rate!
Captain! If you make a scene,
the Marines will...
This will be the last time I see her.
She's become quite a tough pirate...
Bonney.
A pirate struck a Celestial Dragon!
"Human Shop"?!
Who did what to a Celestial Dragon?!
That's a global taboo.
And it's close to Marine Headquarters.
It's an act of suicide!
It's the Straw Hats again!
Are they trying to protect
a Fish-Man and a Mermaid?!
Look, Straw Hat Luffy.
This is probably an act of treason...
...that no one has managed to pull off...
...in many centuries!
Wait, PX-1.
Dragon.
Iva-chan.
Forgive me for disappearing
without a word.
As a mark of my existence,
I'll quietly leave behind…
...Bonney
and this boy's future.
I couldn't even...
...save a single one of my friends!
That is not true.
This is just the level of the New World.
It is still too soon for your crew.
Don't come here yet.
One day in the future...
...you will be the man who saves the world.
A self-destruct switch?!
How much do you fear Kuma?!
You turned him into a deadly human weapon.
You're at the top of the authority hierarchy!
But if he goes berserk
when we are out of command range,
who will stop him and how?
Well...
Cease this insolence.
You are a paltry hired scientist.
Then, in exchange for installing that into him,
let him keep a bit of his free will!
I've invented a brain circuit
that can toggle between personalities!
If you let me try it...
I gave you an order, Vegapunk.
You will not leave him any free will!
I am a scientist myself.
You cannot trick me.
But then Kuma
and Bonney will never be able to meet again...!
Clank.
I appreciate the sentiment, Vegapunk.
What?! There's no way
you could hear that conversation.
Who was it who gave me superhuman hearing?
"Justice"
Okay!
Today is the day you lose your free will.
I've only known you for two years,
but we had so much fun!
We did.
I think your first mission will be
a fight against the Whitebeard Pirates.
They've ordered a mass deployment
of clone soldiers.
I want you to program me a mission
after that.
Protecting the Straw Hats' ship?!
Until one of their crew comes back,
I want to protect their home.
I will not be around to see
their growth anymore, but...
What are you expecting from that kid?
Something in his actions shakes
the very core of my being.
Nika is merely a legend.
But I instilled into Bonney...
...stories of a warrior who rides the rhythm
of liberation and brings smiles to all.
If there is a hero
who will change this world drastically...
I believe it'll be him.
A revolutionary betting on a pirate...
You've chosen quite a dark horse.
That contradiction is proof of your humanity.
Now, provide me materials
for my scientific research.
We had a deal.
When you push them out of you,
do you lose your memories?
No, it's like a copy.
But it'll vanish when it's touched.
That's fine. I created a system
that allows me to study it from a distance.
Put it right there.
Now, this will be quick.
This is just a clinical process.
I'm a scientist.
So this is...
...my life...
How many people have I troubled?
Troubling others!
Indeed, to live is to cause others trouble!
Kumachi, when did you become a slave?
When I was four.
Me too!
Kumachi!
Since I'm four years older than you,
I have to feed you!
Kumachi!
Kumachi! Kumachi!
I'm full!
I'm full...!
I'm... full...
I'm so happy.
Kumachi...
I'll always...
...always...
...love you.
Don't worry, Ginny.
I'll raise your daughter.
Daddy!
Dad!
Those punks...
...made fun of the stones on my face!
Is it that weird?
But it's a disease. I can't help it.
I'm going to be honest with you.
Your daughter...
...has five years at most to live.
She won't live to see her tenth birthday.
Your mother's dead...
She should be in heaven by now.
Hey, Kuma. You're strong.
Endure! Endure and survive!
Why? I think I'd be better off dead too...
The Warrior of Liberation will come!
He'll come to save you!
Who is that?
I can't take it anymore...
I can't take it!
I don't want to...
...lose anyone else!
Nika?
That's right, he's my idol.
Will he come and free me, too?!
The mass of pain and suffering...
...won't just disappear
until someone accepts it.
Your hands liberated people.
Those are the Hands of Liberation!
Thank you.
If Bonney gets well,
I will gladly accept...
"Dad"
...any fate!
Nika, the Sun God!
One day, he'll come and take you out...
...under the sun, to the freedom of the sea!
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm sure.
I'll be cured in a year and get to go outside!
Next time we meet, let's be out on the sea,
watching the horizon together.
Can't wait!
And I wanna go on many trips!
Bonney.
Ever since I was a child,
I wanted to be a hero who could save the downtrodden and suffering.
Kuma!
Kumachi!
Daddy!
It's curable!
Dad!
I'm so glad!
Thank you!
Troubling others!
Indeed, to live is to cause others trouble!
Your death will be trouble...
...for everyone who's ever loved you!
Listen to me, Kuma.
You are the hero...
For Bonney!
And for us all!
Thank you.
Say, Vegapunk...
Yes, I already know.
Nika?
That's right, he's my idol.
Will he come and free me, too?!
Of course!
Thank you...
...for saving Bonney.
Could you tell her this when you see her?
I wish her a happy...
...tenth birthday.
I can't protect anyone again
mata daremo mamorenai no
It's my fault that the voice is fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
I don't even have time to look down
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
Start moving again, my ship
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the broad sky
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
We
bokura wa
EVERYDAY owarenai
EVERYDAY, can't let this be the end
EVERYDAY makerenai
EVERYDAY, can't be defeated
We have something here to protect
mamoru mono ga koko niwa aru
This may not be what I expected
yosou chigai kamo?
But we can't stop now
tomarenai yo mou
We go on, sharing loneliness
kodoku wo ima wakeai susumu
Don't be afraid
ojikedukuna yo
I'm not the same person I was that day
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare nimo jama dekinai yo
Now, move aside
saa doite
Conquer the world, believe in the future
sekai wo seishite mirai wo shinjite
Count up the nights
ikutsu mono yoru kazoete
What did you see? What did you learn?
nani wo mite nani wo shitte
To realize what was important
taisetsu na koto ni kiduita no